(upbeat music)
The Amazon warehousing and distribution inventory dashboard
provides you with near real time inventory data
and allows you to take actions directly from the page,
making it a valuable tool for inventory management.
To access the dashboard in Seller Central,
go to the Inventory dropdown menu
and then select warehousing and distribution, AWD.
Inventory data can be filtered by SKU.
You can also sort inventory data for your SKUs
by clicking on a column.
For example, all SKUs in AWD.
All the data is refreshed near real time,
except for available in FBA, which is refreshed daily.
The dashboard also allows you to take action
on your inventory.
To take actions like sending inventory to AWD,
the action menu can be found
on the right side of the dashboard.
If you believe Amazon's auto replenishment
won't be enough to meet expected sales,
you can also manually move inventory
by clicking move from AWD on the top right corner
of the page.
Have any questions?
More detailed information and instructions
on how to navigate the dashboard can be found
on the AWD Inventory Help page.